umano.me 2015-03-17

# Umano | Privacy

**Effective Date: September 20, 2012**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the SoThree, Inc. Terms of Use . The term "SoThree, Inc.” includes SoThree, Inc., Inc., its affiliates, and SoThree.com. It explains how SoThree, Inc. may: collect, use, and disclose information it obtains through the Service.

The "Service" is defined as any websites, Facebook pages, Facebook applications, mobile application, or other Internet service under the control of SoThree, Inc.. 

**Policy Scope.** This Privacy Policy covers how SoThree, Inc. treats personal information ("Personal Information") and other information that SoThree, Inc. collects through the Service. 

**Personal Information Defined.** SoThree, Inc. considers Personal Information to be information that alone or in combination with other easily available information can allow identification of an individual, including name, address, email address, and/or phone number. SoThree, Inc. does not consider Personal Information to include information that has been anonymized. SoThree shall treat information that is associated with Personal Information as Personal Information.

**Use and Acceptance.** By using this website and accepting the Terms of Use, you also agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept this Privacy Policy, you must not use the Service. 

If you use the Service through Facebook or some other third-party service, you may be required to read and accept their terms of service and privacy policy to use the Service.

**New Uses of Personal Information and Other Information.** From time to time, SoThree, Inc. may use Personal Information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If its information practices change regarding information previously collected, SoThree, Inc. will take reasonable efforts to provide notice and obtain consent to any such uses as may be required by law.

**Posting of Revised Privacy Policy.** SoThree, Inc. will post any adjustments to the Privacy Policy on this web page. The revised version will be effective at the time it is posted. If you are concerned about how your information is used, bookmark this page and read the Privacy Policy periodically.

**Other Websites and Pages.** When you navigate away from the Service to websites controlled by third parties, you leave the Service, at which point this Privacy Policy no longer applies. You will not receive a notice warning when you leave the Service.

**HOW THE SERVICE COLLECTS YOUR INFORMATION**

**PERSONAL INFORMATION Collection.** The Service collects Personal Information when you register. In registering with the Service, you will provide information necessary to use the Service, such as an email and password. SoThree, Inc. may also collect Personal Information from you in other ways, such as contacts with our customer-support team. The Service may also ask for permission to your contacts. If granted, SoThree, Inc., does not store a copy of your contacts on their servers or sell your contacts to any third-parties.

When you access the Service through Facebook, SoThree, Inc. may obtain information you have shared with Facebook. For example, Facebook may share with the Service your information, including: your gender, your profile picture, your birthday, your user ID, your email address, your profile information, your networks, who your friends are, and your friend’s profile information. You control what information is shared from your Facebook profile by adjusting your Facebook privacy settings.

SoThree, Inc. may also collect information about you from your use of the Service, such as your "likes” and the comments you post.

**Cookies, Automatic Data Collection, and Related Technologies.** In addition, the Service collects and stores information that is generated automatically as you use it. This information is collected website-wide, and includes anonymous website statistics. To collect this information, the Service may use log files, web beacons, cookies, and other similar technologies.

For example, the Service uses browser cookies to store users’ preferences and website activity session information. "Cookies” are bits of information that are stored by your browser on your computer. This technology allows for the storage of user preferences, user ID, and password. You can turn off the "cookie” function in most standard Internet browsers; however, the majority of the features of the Service may not function properly without them.

The Service automatically collects other system information, such as your web request; Internet Protocol ("IP”) address; browser type; browser language; domain names; referring and exit pages and URLs; platform type; number of clicks; landing pages; page and pages titles viewed and the order of these page views; the amount of time spent on particular pages; the date and time of your request; the unique identity of your browser; whether your browser enables Java, cookies, or other applications and plugins; your server type; the country, state, and telephone area code where your servers are located; the number of visits and searches you make; and any search terms you enter using the Service. This information is aggregated and used to analyze trends, administer the Service, improve the design of the Service, track user movement, and otherwise enhance the Service. SoThree, Inc. may also use this information to determine Users’ preferences and interests and to match with User demographics.

By using the Service, you are authorizing us to gather, parse, and retain data related to the provision of the Service.

**HOW SOTHREE USES YOUR INFORMATION**

**Contacting You.** SoThree, Inc. may use your email address to send you promotional materials and to communicate with you concerning services.

**Internal and Service-related Usage.** SoThree, Inc. uses Personal Information for internal and service-related purposes to enhance and personalize your use of the Service and may use third parties to allow us to offer the Service. For example, SoThree, Inc. may use information about your "like” of the displayed content using the Service to suggest brands and offers to match your interests.

SoThree, Inc. does not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies for marketing purposes without your consent.

SoThree, Inc. may allow access to non-Personal Information collected by the Service to enable the delivery of marketing and offers that will be of greatest utility, relevance, value, and interest to you.

By using our Service you understand and agree that we are providing a platform for you feature your own profile picture and to post likes and comments ("User Content") to the Service and to share User Content publicly. This means that User Content may also be available and visible on other third party platforms and on the web, made publicly available through the Service, consistent with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

**WHEN SOTHREE MAY DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION**

**As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures**. SoThree, Inc. may access, preserve, and disclose your Personal Information, other account information, and content if it believes doing so is required by law or if those actions are reasonably necessary to:

(1) comply with legal process, such as a court order or subpoena;

(2) enforce this Privacy Policy or these Terms; 

(3) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties;

(4) respond to your requests for customer service;

(5) respond to law enforcement;

(6) investigate and prevent unauthorized transactions or other illegal activities; or 

(7) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of SoThree, Inc., its users, or the public.

**SoThree, Inc. System and Related Security.** SoThree, Inc. may disclose information about you, including data on which pages you have visited and other information regarding your use of the Service, to third parties if, in its sole discretion, such disclosure is necessary to protect its systems, website, business, users or others.

**Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers.** Information about you in SoThree, Inc.’s possession may be disclosed as part of a merger, acquisition, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which your Personal Information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. SoThree, Inc. does not guarantee that any entity receiving such information in connection with one of these transactions will comply with all terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Vendors and Suppliers.** SoThree, Inc. may share any information with third-party vendors and suppliers retained in connection with the provision of the Service. The third party’s use of that information may be subject to its own restrictions. We make no promises and are not responsible for the third party’s intended use, use, or security of the information.

SoThree, Inc. may also disclose your Personal Information with your permission.

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

When SoThree, Inc. handles information that you disclose through the Service, regardless of where this occurs, SoThree, Inc. takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this policy. Unfortunately, SoThree, Inc. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit through the Service, and you do so at your own risk. SoThree, Inc. does not accept liability for unintentional disclosure.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

SoThree, Inc. does not knowingly collect, maintain, or use any Personal Information from children under 13 years of age. No part of the Service is directed to persons under the age of 13. In fact, you must be at least 13 years of age to set up an account with the Service. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE SERVICE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER.

If SoThree, Inc. becomes aware that it has collected any Personal Information from children under 13, it will promptly delete such information from its databases. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under the age of 13 has obtained a Service account, then you may alert SoThree, Inc. at HYPERLINK "mailto:info@SoThree.com" info@SoThree.com and request that SoThree, Inc. delete that child’s Personal Information from our systems.

**INTERNATIONAL USERS**

By choosing to visit the Service or otherwise provide information to SoThree, Inc., you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the law of the state of New York. 

**If you are accessing the Service from any physical location with regulations or laws governing personal data collection, use, or disclosure that differ from United States regulations or laws, please note that through your continued use of the Service, you are transferring Personal Information to the United States of America or other jurisdiction where such information may be processed and you consent to that transfer.**

You also consent to the adjudication of any disputes arising in connection with SoThree, Inc. or the Service in accordance with the Terms of Use.

**UPDATE YOUR INFORMATION OR POSE A QUESTION OR SUGGESTION**

If you would like to update or correct any information that you have provided to SoThree, Inc. through your use of the Service or otherwise, please send an email to info@SoThree.com.

SoThree, Inc. reserves the right to send you certain communications relating to SoThree, Inc., such as service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your SoThree, Inc. account.

**Contact Info**

SoThree

300 Brannan Street, Suite 302

San Francisco, CA, 94107
